[theme music playing]
Emilia had him killed.
I'll kill her!
[Ivy] I need to leave again.
They found a lead on Arthur's whereabouts.
There's a possibility that
Arthur escaped from the drum.
-Mr. Mayor!
-Ivy!
-Mr. Mayor, she's not here!
[Arnaldo] Then why is her cell phone here?
-She left it behi--
-Liar!
[Carlotta gasps]
Ivy!
Ivy, come out here! Open the door!
-Nanny?
-Ivy… Ivy, the…
-[Arnaldo screams]
[Carlotta choking]
[Ivy] I think something happened
to Nanny Carlotta.
Nanny Carlotta?
[Ivy screaming and wailing]
Who did this to you?!
[police officer] We can't find
any signs of foul play.
It looks like a suicide, Miss Aguas.
Do you know what that murderer did?
They wiped the crime scene clean
to make it look like
Nanny Carlotta committed suicide.
[Julio] What do you know about the death
of Ivy Aguas' sweet old nanny?
[Arnaldo] I lost control of my emotions!
I went there because Diego
started making a move on Ivy.
You shouldn't have let
that woman get into your head.
[Diego] Ivy, I know what you're thinking.
You know who's behind
Miss Carlotta's murder.
It was one of the Ardientes.
[Ivy] Nanny, help me find
the monster who killed you.
I'll find out who that person is,
and I'll make them pay.
A-A-T.
Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
What do you have to do
with Nanny Carlotta's death?
Where's the other cufflink?
I'm sorry, Mayor,
but I'm afraid there wasn't any--
-Just admit you messed up!
-I'm sorry.
Get out of my face!
If you can't find it,
I'll shove this down your throat!
Now go!
Arnaldo.
What's going on? Why are you shouting?
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
The maids lost one
of the cufflinks you gave me.
The one with your initials?
Yes.
Weren't you
wearing it yesterday?
Are you sure you didn't leave it
at Ivy Aguas' house?
[tense music playing]
No.
Impossible.
I made sure they wouldn't find
any evidence.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
We cleaned the place up.
I made sure, okay?
[exhales]
[tense music playing]
Ivy.
Arnaldo.
[cries]
I heard what happened.
I wanted to see you, but--
[crying]
We Ardientes offer
our condolences, Miss Aguas.
Thank you.
Can you tell me what happened?
Nanny Carlotta called me before she died.
When I came home, it was too late.
I saw her body hanging, Arnaldo.
[stutters] I'm sorry, I wasn't there.
I've been trying to call you.
Where were you?
I know.
I'm sorry, I'm here now.
Arnaldo.
[suspenseful music playing]
Sit down, sit down.
What happened to your hand?
This?
Um…
I was blowing off some steam
at the firing range.
It's a stupid mistake.
I cocked the gun the wrong way.
Anyway…
I just want to say sorry.
I wasn't there when you needed me.
I was too busy with the campaign.
I didn't realize there was
no reception in the area.
It won't happen again.
I promise.
[tense music swells]
Diego.
Lily's not picking up my calls.
She probably wants to
spend some time alone.
[sighs]
I want to comfort my daughter…
but I can't be with her.
I can't let the Ardientes know
that I'm her mother.
We both feel the same way.
I can't do the things
I want to do for her…
because it might ruin her plans.
Like loving her.
But I'm not giving up.
I'll wait for her.
[soft piano music playing]
[tense music playing]
Arnaldo.
Take me away.
I want to get out of this town.
Yes. I'll do that.
I'll do that. I'll take you away.
We'll go somewhere far away.
I'll make you forget everything.
Come here.
[Arnaldo] Hey, what's wrong?
What's this?
Is this yours?
Yeah, that's mine.
I've been looking for it.
[tense music intensifies]
Lily, why did you do that?
You shouldn't have gone
to the Ardientes' mansion alone.
What if you're right,
and they had something to do
with Carlotta's death?
What if they kill you next?
Nanny Carlotta was murdered
for a different reason.
Like what?
That's what I'll find out.
After the cremation,
I'll go on a vacation.
I'll be gone for a few days.
And where are you going?
I asked Arnaldo to decide.
I'm not sure, either.
You're leaving with Arnaldo?
Okay, I'll be gone for a few days,
but the work here doesn't stop.
In fact, you'll work double time
because I want this campaign
running without me.
Mayor, how can we run
the campaign without you?
The voters want to see you.
The last time I checked,
I pay you to think of solutions,
and not to give me more problems.
So, do whatever it takes.
You can invite celebrities,
hire sexy dancers,
or do any gimmicks
to fill our events with people.
So, I want a clear plan
of action by noon today. Go.
Yes, Mayor.
You know, Arnaldo…
I have a strong feeling that
your obsession with Ivy Aguas…
will be the cause of your downfall.
Just relax, Grandpa.
Ivy is an inspiration,
and she's the reason
why I'm working so hard.
So, leave her alone.
What did she do, for you
to be head over heels for her?
Has she given you the works?
Well, not yet.
But we'll get there.
Don't laugh because
I'm not joking with you.
I'm warning you.
Be careful when you're around that woman,
because if she finds out what you did…
then I'll be forced to kill her,
and you know I won't hesitate.
Understand?
[sighs]
[tense music intensifies]
[Julio] Here she comes!
Arnaldo!
What's this I heard from your staff
about you going on a vacation?
You know, Emilia,
you arrived at the perfect time.
Talk to your son.
Because you're very similar.
You're both fools for love.
[Julio laughs]
Hey, what's going on?
[Julio sighs]
Ivy. Ivy, wait.
I know you're only doing this
to get back at them.
But what are you planning to do?
Ivy, why won't you tell me?
Don't you trust me?
This isn't about trust.
It's just better that none of you know.
Diego.
Let's be patient with Lily.
Whatever she's doing…
I know she has her reasons.
[Diego] I understand.
I'm just worried because
what she's doing is dangerous.
Diego, I feel the same.
I'm worried too.
Even though I know
Lily can handle herself…
as her mother, I'm still scared for her.
Diego just promise me…
you'll protect my daughter.
I promise.
If only I could stay
by her side all the time,
I would.
But now I have other things
to take care of.
Where are you going?
I'm going to look for Arthur.
If he really is alive,
I know the Ardientes are hunting him down.
I'll convince him to testify against them.
I'm sorry that I have
to keep secrets from you.
But I have to avenge
Nanny Carlotta's death.
You don't have to be part of this.
I can't let others experience
what happened to Nanny Carlotta and Jepoy.
[Ivy] The Ardientes won't hurt
any of my loved ones again.
You will not go with that woman alone.
I'm not a child anymore.
I can do whatever I want.
Arnaldo, my son!
That woman's got you on a leash.
Who knows? She might just
dupe you into marrying her!
Ivy's different.
She's not like you.
Excuse me, Arnaldo,
but I didn't trick your father.
Yeah, right.
Listen to me.
I don't like that woman for you.
I don't trust her.
Well, you can say whatever you want, okay?
But my feelings for Ivy won't change,
and that's final.
Excuse me.
[ominous music playing]
Mister.
Mister, can I ask you something?
Good evening. Can I ask you something?
-What is it?
-Uh…
Do you recognize this man?
I think I've seen him.
Really?
When did you see him?
I can't remember when,
but I've seen this man.
He probably lives around here.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
What did Papa say?
Are we going to Carlotta's wake?
I don't know, and I don't care.
Honestly, I'd rather relax or go to a spa
than go there
to put up with Ivy wailing over
the death of her foster mother.
You know, she's just craving attention.
Emilia, I was just asking a question.
Don't stress yourself over it.
How about I just give you a massage?
Wait, Raul. Hold on.
Did you do something wrong again?
Are you cheating on me again?
No! I'm just being a good husband.
A good husband? Why?
Why, is that a big deal?
If you don't like it, then fine!
I'll go back to my old self.
I didn't mean that.
Stop it, you.
Okay, how about this, Emilia?
Have dinner with me,
and we'll talk about things
that need to be discussed.
Let's fix everything as husband and wife.
Wait.
Are you asking me out on a date?
I don't know.
But I just want to be with you.
Wow.
What's gotten into you?
Nothing.
Arthur.
When do you plan on going to the police?
After everything I've been through
at the hands of the Ardientes?
I don't want to come out of hiding.
What about your fight for justice?
There is no justice in Poblacion Ardiente.
They're going to kill anyone
who stands in their way.
I'd rather have them think I'm dead.
I'll do everything…
even if it means I have to kill…
just to keep them from
finding out I'm still alive.
This one's strong!
-Hmm?
-Hi.
Hi.
Raul Torillo.
-I know.
-Raul Torillo.
-Hi.
-You are?
I'm Emilia.
[both laughing]
-What are you doing?
-Too cheesy?
Is it just me,
or is there something about tonight?
It's like…
What are you talking about?
-This is how we met.
-[giggles]
-Right?
-Yes, I remember.
We'd always have fun like this.
Exactly like this.
I know. That's why we're here.
We're having fun, aren't we?
Is that why you brought me here?
Yes. Because I wanted us to have fun.
-Okay?
-I see.
How do I know this isn't just for tonight?
Emilia.
I'm sure you feel it too, don't you?
Prove it.
[giggling]
I'm serious, okay?
Okay.
I want you back.
I want things back the way they were.
I want us to be happy.
Not a problem in the world.
Although, we do have a few now.
But we'll just laugh them off.
Or, better yet,
we can just stay in our room.
-Right?
-[both giggle]
No, I'm serious. I really am.
If you want me to court you, I'll do it.
-Really?
-I will.
[giggling]
[Emilia giggles]
-What? Okay.
-People are watching.
You love me, right?
-Of course, you do.
-Should I say yes now?
You don't have to answer that.
Just kiss me.
Just kiss me then, that's it.
I'm good with that.
Oh, my goodness. It's actually working.
She's so desperate.
This is the beginning
of your downfall, Emilia.
[Raul and Emilia laugh]
[ominous music playing]
She's in a better place now.
[cries]
Why did this have to happen, Arnaldo?
I wish I could dream of Nanny Carlotta.
So she could tell me…
who did this to her.
[tense music playing]
[fakes crying]
[phone ringing]
[Camia] Diego?
Aunt Camia.
Someone spotted Arthur.
[Diego] I'll keep going back there until…
I find him.
[Camia] Diego, just be careful, okay?
The Ardientes can't
find out he's still alive.
Yes, Aunt Camia.
I have to go now.
Take care, Diego.
[car engine turns over]
Nanny, make this the centerpiece, okay?
Clean this later.
So beautiful. [giggles]
Hi, Auntie.
You're blooming.
-Did you have fun last night?
-[laughs]
You're so naughty, Aunt Claire.
Well, that smile of yours
reminds me of a giggling teenager.
Well, that's what love can do, Auntie.
It makes you feel young again.
So, you're in love?
At last!
You finally called it quits with Raul.
So, tell me, who's the lucky guy?
Auntie, there's no new guy.
It's still the same.
I still love Raul.
From then on and forever,
he will always be the love of my life.
Raul is like wine.
The longer it's aged, the better it gets.
Disgusting.
When will you stop believing Raul's lies?
Auntie, we talked over dinner last night.
He told me he would court me again,
that he'd change,
that he loves me very much.
I already heard that.
Your husband is cunning.
So if I were you,
test him first before
believing anything he says.
Auntie, you're so pessimistic.
You became an old maid
because you always think like that.
You know, if there's one thing
I learned about love…
Nothing is impossible with love.
You know why I didn't get married?
Because all men are liars.
And your husband is no exception.
Auntie, you're such a man-hater.
Now I'm curious who turned you into one.
Why so bitter?
Just give me more time.
Okay, Natalie?
Okay.
But I've just realized,
you really are a bastard.
I actually love it.
-Really? I'm a bastard?
-Mm-hm.
-Yes, you are.
-Okay.
[both giggle]
-Am I a bastard?
-Yeah!
[Raul laughs]
Excuse me. Good evening.
-What is it?
-Can I ask you a question?
Do you recognize this man?
I haven't seen this guy around.
Maybe he's from another village.
Okay, thank you.
[woman whispers] We should hurry.
Are you okay, ma'am?
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Your basket is broken.
-You aren't from here, are you?
-I'm not.
I can tell.
I'm looking for someone.
Maybe you recognize this man.
[tense music playing]
Have you seen him before?
No, I haven't. I don't know him.
I'm going now. Please give me that.
[tense music intensifies]
Arthur! Arthur!
-Yes?
-Arthur!
You have to leave!
Somebody's looking for you.
Who is it?
I don't know, but maybe…
he's one of the men who wanted you dead.
Hurry!
He might find you here.
Arthur!
Diego?
We need to talk.
Arthur, wait!
Listen, Arthur!
I won't testify against the Ardientes!
Arthur, hear me out first.
Please. Arthur.
Please listen to me?
You shouldn't have looked for me.
Mister Arthur, wait.
I won't put you in danger.
I'll make sure we have
enough evidence in court…
before you give your testimony.
I'm living a quiet life!
You can't ruin it!
Arthur, you can't hide forever.
If I found you, the Ardientes
will find you too!
Arthur, you need us.
We'll help you!
I know you're a good person.
You're not capable of murder.
[tense music intensifies]
Arthur.
Arthur, let's talk.
I'll help you.
We'll help you.
[tense music continues playing]
[cries]
Arthur.
Put the gun down.
I'm going to take Ivy to our resort.
So, if you need me,
you know where to find me.
But…
I hope I don't see you
the whole time I'm with her.
Arnaldo, what's wrong with you?
First, it was Natalie. Now it's Ivy!
Your taste in women is getting worse!
[Julio] You know…
they say that men
fall in love with women who
are similar to their mothers.
Therefore, parents are to blame
for their children's mistakes.
That is why I can never forgive myself
for what happened to you.
Papa, please, can you just help me out?
Let's convince Arnaldo
not to go on this trip with Ivy!
-I'll convince him.
-Go on.
What are you doing, Papa?! Wait!
You mean to tell me not
even a bullet in his head
is going to convince him
to change his mind?!
[laughs]
My dear grandson, Arnaldo.
I asked you to romance Ivy
so we could take her money.
Now, getting her to bed
is just a bonus for you.
That's for your ego.
I can't understand you.
You're handsome, you're rich,
and you're a mayor!
But when it comes to Ivy,
she's got you eating
from the palm of her hand!
You're like a hound dog
being led to slaughter.
Every time Ivy comes up…
[mimics whining dog]
Am I right? You think that's funny?!
It's not funny!
Remember, from time immemorial,
Adam and Eve.
It was Eve who was seduced
and fooled by the snake.
But at this rate, you're going
to get bitten by the snake!
I can't understand you!
Well, I think he's
pushing through with it.
I just hope this time you get the cherry!
[suspenseful music playing]
[sinister music playing]
Mr. Mayor, I want you to choose
which one of these
I should use to kill you.
[sinister music intensifies]
[phone rings]
Mom?
I've already packed my stuff,
including the important things.
My staff are preparing the house
I'll move into.
After my trip, I'll head there right away.
Yes, I'll be careful.
Thank you, Mom.
I promise you, Nanny Carlotta.
I'll make sure…
I make Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo pay.
You're really funny.
Well, anyway, just enjoy the beach,
and make sure nothing bad
happens to Arnaldo.
You know what?
I think you should
stay there alone for good.
If you're envious, then just join us.
No, thanks.
I don't want you to drown me there.
Impressive.
You read my mind.
What about you?
Do you have any idea what I'm thinking?
I'm not interested.
Well, I know you're only using Arnaldo
to get close to our family.
But let me just warn you.
You're messing with the wrong family.
You really love your family, don't you?
I do.
You're like a mother hen.
Sad to say,
they don't like you.
[laughs]
You're testing my patience.
Emilia.
What's wrong?
That's enough.
So…
you two are getting along now.
Why are you so cranky,
if you're happy now?
You're making me envious. Where's Arnaldo?
Arthur has agreed to testify for us again.
To ensure his safety,
we have to make sure
we have enough evidence
before he presents himself in court.
That's good to hear.
Where's Ivy?
Hasn't she told you?
She's leaving with Arnaldo today.
Miss Aguas, the mayor's here.
Arnaldo.
Ivy.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
The conference just finished.
-But we can go now.
-It's okay.
-Shall we?
-Okay.
Diego, I need your help.
Please follow them.
And watch over my daughter.
-Let's go.
All right. Bye.
-Shouldn't we see them out?
-Bye, Emilia.
[Emilia] Good grief.
That Arnaldo still hasn't
learned his lesson.
Relax, Emilia.
Our son is an adult.
He knows what he's doing.
But he is falling for the wrong girl.
Why Ivy, of all people?
Of all the women in the world, why her?
We can't tell our son who to love.
But as his parents,
we just have to support him.
Wait, are we actually
discussing this as parents?
Because this is the first time
we've done this.
And I hope this won't be
the last to save our marriage.
We need to fix our family.
Especially my relationship with Arnaldo.
Emilia, to be a better husband,
I have to be a good father.
[phone ringing]
What do you want?
Hello, Diego.
I hope you remember me…
your former mom.
[Emilia] I hope you didn't
delete my number.
I don't have the time to talk to you.
Ivy and Arnaldo are going on a vacation.
Now, do you have the time to talk?
What makes you think I'm interested?
Come on, Diego. I know you.
We're the same.
When we love, we go all in.
You know I'm right.
I'm sure you won't let Arnaldo
have Ivy to himself, right?
Where are they going?
To our beach resort in La Union.
I think you've been there…
when you were still an Ardiente.
But I have a favor to ask.
I hope it doesn't get out that
I gave you this information.
Because even at gunpoint,
I will never admit to it.
Why should I trust you?
Because I don't want my son
to end up with that bitch.
I just know she's better off with you.
So, what are you waiting for?
Go get your girl.
Hurry.
[upbeat music playing]
Do you like it?
[Ivy giggles]
Do you really have to ask?
Of course, I do.
Thanks for bringing me here.
Good.
No one can disturb us here.
It's just you, me…
and this paradise.
Perfect.
What's this?
Diego, where are you going?
I'll be going out for a bit, Nanny.
But I've told the group
what to do with the campaign
while I'm gone.
Where are you going, son?
I'll follow Ivy and Arnaldo.
I need to protect Ivy
because I don't trust Arnaldo.
But, Diego, what if--
Nanny, let me do this.
Nothing bad will happen to me.
All right. Do what you have to do.
Just be careful, okay?
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
I'm going now, Nanny.
-Uncle.
-Be safe.
-Just take care.
-I will.
Thank you!
Good morning, sir. Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
[Arnaldo] I'll just check in here.
-Is our room ready?
-[woman] Yes, sir.
[suspenseful music playing]
Okay, good.
[metal detector beeps]
Ma'am, can we open your luggage?
Why?
For inspection, ma'am.
Is there a problem?
And you are?
Special Police Officer 3 Umali,
Congressman.
I'm one of the investigating officers
assigned to Carlotta Naig's suicide case.
Mayor Arnaldo ordered me
to make sure the crime scene
was cleaned up.
Good job, Umali.
They didn't find any evidence.
Thank you, Congressman.
What brings you here?
Do you need your bonus now?
No, Congressman.
I came here to warn the mayor.
The police didn't find any
evidence leading to foul play.
But, Congressman, no matter what we do,
Ivy won't change her mind.
Ivy is convinced
that her nanny was murdered.
She's determined to catch and punish
whoever murdered Carlotta.
So, Congressman,
if Miss Aguas invited the mayor
to go somewhere
she can have him to herself,
he should be careful.
Miss Aguas might be planning
something against him.
Thank you, Umali.
That's very sound advice
that you just gave me.
Anything for you, Congressman.
I'll be on my way.
-Okay.
-Excuse me.
Well, I don't have any problem with that.
But it'll be such a hassle.
Do you really have to do that?
You don't need to check her
things because she's my visitor.
I'm Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo,
and my family owns this place.
Get her things now.
I'm sorry, sir. Sheryl will assist you.
Arnaldo, thank you.
Let's go.
-Please, have a drink.
-Welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mayor.
Okay.
Ivy, this is your room.
I'll just be in the next one.
So you can call me any time.
Thank you.
You know, this place is quiet at night.
It gets lonely.
So?
So…
I'm suggesting
we share a room.
It would be more fun.
[Ivy giggles]
Arnaldo, you're always excited.
Can you blame me?
I just want to make
the most out of this trip.
It pays to be patient, Arnaldo.
It pays to be patient.
Why are you playing hard to get?
Just don't give up.
I promise you, all your effort
and all the time you've waited…
It will be worth it.
Promise.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] Who's that from?
It's from a certain Jaguar.
Jaguar? I've never heard that name before.
This newcomer has some nerve.
[Ivy] Why are you here?
[Diego] I'm here to watch over you.
I don't trust Arnaldo.
You'll ruin my plans.
What do you want me to do?
Kneel before me.
Kiss my feet.
Worship me.
Don't worry about Arnaldo.
I can protect myself.
[theme music playing]